export default {

  difficulty1: [
    {
      question: 'What operating system did Google develop?',
      response1: 'Android',
      response2: 'BlackBerry OS',
      response3: 'Windows',
      response4: 'iOS',
      correctAnswer: '1',
      time: '10',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'Which of these is not a peripheral, in computer terms?',
      response1: 'Keyboard',
      response2: 'Mouse',
      response3: 'Monitor',
      response4: 'Motherboard',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '10',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'Which of these is not one of the early “protocols,” or ways to use the Internet?',
      response1: 'Telnet',
      response2: 'FTP',
      response3: 'HTTP',
      response4: 'Blogging',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'What does the Internet prefix WWW stand for?',
      response1: 'Wide Width Wickets',
      response2: 'World Wide Weather',
      response3: 'World Wide Web',
      response4: 'Western Washington World',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'A network designed to allow communication within an organization is called:',
      response1: 'An intranet',
      response2: 'The World Wide Web',
      response3: 'A browser',
      response4: 'The Internet',
      correctAnswer: '1',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '1',
    },
  ],

  difficulty2: [
    {
      question: 'What does the acronym FTP stand for?',
      response1: 'File Tripling Power',
      response2: 'Free Transfer Protocol',
      response3: 'File Transfer Protocol',
      response4: 'Fast Total Processing',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: 'Computer trojans are an example of:',
      response1: 'Malware',
      response2: 'Spyware',
      response3: 'Computer worms',
      response4: 'Network Security Devices',
      correctAnswer: '1',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: 'Which of these was the first programmable general-purpose electronic digital computer?',
      response1: 'EDVAC',
      response2: 'ENIAC',
      response3: 'BINAC',
      response4: 'Acorn Network Computer',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: 'Which of these education-oriented computer languages was developed by Niklaus Wirth?',
      response1: 'Pascal',
      response2: 'BASIC',
      response3: 'Hypertalk',
      response4: 'LOGO',
      correctAnswer: '1',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: 'Who created the computer-programming language FORTRAN?',
      response1: 'Bill Atkinson',
      response2: 'John McCarthy',
      response3: 'John Backus',
      response4: 'Dennis Ritchie',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '2',
    },
  ],

  difficulty3: [
    {
      question: 'What device, released in 1993, gave rise to the term personal digital assistant?',
      response1: 'iPhone',
      response2: 'Microsoft Surface',
      response3: 'Newton MessagePad',
      response4: 'Palm Pilot',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: 'What was the name of the chess-playing computer that made history when\nit defeated world champion Garry Kasparov in 1996?',
      response1: 'Deep Thought',
      response2: 'Deep Blue',
      response3: 'Rybka',
      response4: 'Chiptest',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: "Who coined the term 'artificial intelligence' in 1956?",
      response1: 'Charles Bachman',
      response2: 'John McCarthy',
      response3: 'Herbert A, Simon',
      response4: 'Donald Ervin Knuth',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: 'Who invented the distributed network as well as data packet switching\nacross distributed networks?',
      response1: 'Steven Ballmer',
      response2: 'Jean Bartik',
      response3: 'Manuel Blum',
      response4: 'Paul Baran',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: 'Who is known as the first computer programmer?',
      response1: 'Steve Jobs',
      response2: 'Charles Babbage',
      response3: 'Alan Turing',
      response4: 'Ada Lovelace',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },
  ],
};
